{
    "id": "44b9d21348c44b39b5a1764763f03898",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The snake crawled ………………… its hole.",
            "description": "Into is used in speaking of things in motion.",
            "answers": [
                "into",
                "in",
                "onto"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The boys jumped ………………… the river.",
            "description": "Into is used in speaking of things in motion.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "to",
                "into"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The cat sprang …………………… the table.",
            "description": "On is used in speaking of things at rest, and upon is used in speaking of things in motion.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "upon"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He sat ……………………. a bench.",
            "description": "On indicates position on the surface of something. ",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We walked …………………… the end of the street.",
            "description": "Until is only used to talk about time. To talk about distance, we use up to or as far as.",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "till",
                "up to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You can earn ………………… 500 dollars a week in this job.",
            "description": "Up to is also used to talk about quantity.",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "up to",
                "as far as"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He killed two birds …………………. one shot.",
            "description": "With denotes the instrument and by denotes the agent.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The traveler was stabbed ……………………. a lunatic.",
            "description": "With denotes the instrument and by denotes the agent.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I have done nothing ………………………. morning.",
            "description": "Since indicates the starting point of an action. It is usually preceded by a perfect or perfect continuous tense.",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They will join school …………………… tomorrow.",
            "description": "From also indicates the starting point. However, it is mainly used with simple tenses. It can also refer to the future. ",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "from",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Human sacrifices were practiced ……………………… the Nagas.",
            "description": "By denotes the agent - the person(s) or thing(s) that commit(s) the action. ",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "with",
                "after"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………. his children, there were present his nephews and nieces.",
            "description": "Beside means by the side of besides means in addition to.",
            "answers": [
                "Beside",
                "Besides"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}